<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Sharing on ownCloud Product</title>
    <link>https://owncloud.github.io/product/sharing/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Sharing on ownCloud Product</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="https://owncloud.github.io/product/sharing/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Collaborators</title>
      <link>https://owncloud.github.io/product/sharing/collaborators/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://owncloud.github.io/product/sharing/collaborators/</guid>
      <description>This document describes the features around &amp;lsquo;Collaborators&amp;rsquo; from the perspective of the owner. The perspective of a recipient is described in the section &amp;lsquo;Resources&amp;rsquo;.
User stories Requirements Adding collaborators to a resource  As an owner or co-owner of a resource I want to be able to add other collaborators to the resource in order to provide access and to enable collaboration on the resource.  1 2 3 4 5 6 7 8 9 10 11 12 13 14 15 16 17 18 19 20 21 22 23 24 25  Feature: Adding collaborators to a resource Scenario: Finding collaborators GIVEN I&amp;#39;m a logged in user located in the collaborators panel of a resource WHEN I start typing in the collaborator search field THEN I see suggestions (with potentially many characters) based on the available user and group identifiers/attributes, sharing restrictions and options for autocomplete results.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Links</title>
      <link>https://owncloud.github.io/product/sharing/links/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://owncloud.github.io/product/sharing/links/</guid>
      <description>This document describes the features around &amp;lsquo;Links&amp;rsquo; from the perspective of the owner. The perspective of a recipient is described in the section &amp;lsquo;Resources&amp;rsquo;.
User stories  Private Link  As a user I want to be able to refer to shared resources by posting a static link (that never changes) on other media like email, chat rooms   Link that can grant access (Public Link)  As a user (owner) I want to collaborate on any resource quickly &amp;amp; easily with anybody.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>